Secretary of the Faculty for Arts, Sciences and Engineering Records UA037
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Secretary of the Faculty for Arts, Sciences and Engineering Records
1854 -- 2019
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Arts and Sciences
Secretary of the Faculty
Graduate School of Arts and Sciences
School of Engineering
Jackson College
UA037
25.0 Linear Feet 22 boxes
55 Volumes
433 Digital Object(s) Of the 433 digital objects, one contains 1,648 files.
1.3 Gigabytes
The records consist of the minutes of faculty meetings in Tufts College, and later the schools of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences and the College of Engineering.
Arrangement
The collection is organized in four series: Faculty meeting minutes; Subject and committee files; and Official papers, and Unprocessed accessions.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of the minutes of faculty meetings as well as supporting documentation. They record the actions taken by the faculty of Tufts College, and later the schools of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences (College of Liberal Arts, Jackson College, and the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences) and the College of Engineering. The records of the Fletcher School and the Medical, Dental and Veterinary, and Nutrition Schools are kept within each school's records.
Related Materials
UA193, University Microfilm Collection, DCA
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Biographical / Historical
The Secretary of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences was established in 1854, and has remained a position in the university's administration to the present day. The position's primary function has been to support faculty members in the school of Arts and Sciences through various means. This has entailed keeping minutes and agendas of regular faculty meetings. It has also necessitated the maintenance of subject files regarding various committees, curricula, and student life. Additionally, the Secretary of the Faculty facilitates communication between faculty of the Arts and Sciences, faculty of the School of Engineering, and the university administration. This responsibility has taken various forms, including keeping track of records from secretaries of the School of Engineering, and Tufts' graduate schools.
Curriculum and Instruction -- Faculty; Administration and Governance
- Faculty meeting minutes, 1854 -- 2019; UA037.001; 9.4 Linear Feet; 55 Volumes; 431 Digital Object(s); 938 Megabytes 429 of 431 digital objects comprise 938 megabytes.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains meeting agendas, minutes, and related attachments of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences at Tufts College. Also contains records from the College of Engineering.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  75 years from the date of creation. 20 years from date of creation. Open for research.
  - Faculty Minutes, vol. 1, 1854-10-09 -- 1862-02-24; UA037.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Open for research.
  - Faculty Minutes, vol. 2, 1862-03-03 -- 1864-11-01; UA037.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, vol. 3, 1864-11-01 -- 1870-07-01; UA037.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, vol. 4, 1870-08-30 -- 1876-12-19; UA037.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, vol. 5, 1877-01-09 -- 1885-01-19; UA037.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, vol. 6, 1885-09-16 -- 1894-04-02; UA037.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, vol. 7, 1894-05-07 -- 1900-06-26; UA037.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, vol. 8, 1900-09-25 -- 1904-01-25; UA037.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, Divinity School, vol. 8A, 1871-07-07 -- 1904-06-15; UA037.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, General Faculty, vol. 8B, 1881-06-06 -- 1894-12-06; UA037.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, Graduate Faculty, vol. 8C, 1892-10-03 -- 1903-11-12; UA037.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, Engineering Faculty, vol. 8D, 1894-03-22 -- 1900-04-10; UA037.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Records, Arts and Sciences, 1903-03-03 -- 1904-01-11; UA037.001.013.001 (Box Volume 13)
  - Records, Administrative Board, 2, 1900 -- 1904; UA037.001.014.001 (Box Volume 14)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 9 & 10, 1903 -- 1905; UA037.001.015.001 (Box Volume 15)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 11 & 12, 1905 -- 1907; UA037.001.016.001 (Box Volume 16)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 13 & 14, 1907 -- 1909; UA037.001.017.001 (Box Volume 17)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 15 & 16, 1909 -- 1911; UA037.001.018.001 (Box Volume 18)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 17 & 18, 1911 -- 1913; UA037.001.019.001 (Box Volume 19)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 19 & 20, 1913 -- 1915; UA037.001.020.001 (Box Volume 20)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 21 & 22, 1915 -- 1917; UA037.001.021.001 (Box Volume 21)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records October 10, 1917-May 24, 1919, Vol. 23-24, 1917 -- 1919; UA037.001.022.001 (Box Volume 22)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 25-26, 1919 -- 1921; UA037.001.023.001 (Box Volume 23)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 27-28, 1921 -- 1923; UA037.001.024.001 (Box Volume 24)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 29-30, 1923 -- 1930; UA037.001.025.001 (Box Volume 25)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 31-32, 1925 -- 1927; UA037.001.026.001 (Box Volume 26)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 33-34, 1927 -- 1929; UA037.001.027.001 (Box Volume 27)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 35-36, 1929 -- 1931; UA037.001.028.001 (Box Volume 28)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 37-38, 1931 -- 1933; UA037.001.029.001 (Box Volume 29)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 39-40, 1933 -- 1935; UA037.001.030.001 (Box Volume 30)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 41-42, 1935 -- 1937; UA037.001.031.001 (Box Volume 31)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 43-44, 1937 -- 1939; UA037.001.032.001 (Box Volume 32)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 45-46, 1939 -- 1941; UA037.001.033.001 (Box Volume 33)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 47-48, 1941 -- 1943; UA037.001.034.001 (Box Volume 34)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 49-50, 1943 -- 1945; UA037.001.035.001 (Box Volume 35)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 51-52, 1945 -- 1947; UA037.001.036.001 (Box Volume 36)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 53-54, 1947 -- 1949; UA037.001.037.001 (Box Volume 37)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 55-56, 1949 -- 1951; UA037.001.038.001 (Box Volume 38)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 57-58, 1951 -- 1953; UA037.001.039.001 (Box Volume 39)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 59-60, 1953 -- 1955; UA037.001.040.001 (Box Volume 40)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 61-62, 1955 -- 1957; UA037.001.041.001 (Box Volume 41)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 63-64, 1957 -- 1959; UA037.001.042.001 (Box Volume 42)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 65-66, 1959 -- 1961; UA037.001.043.001 (Box Volume 43)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 67-68, 1961 -- 1963; UA037.001.044.001 (Box Volume 44)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 69-70, 1963 -- 1965; UA037.001.045.001 (Box Volume 45)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records Vols. 71-72, 1965 -- 1967; UA037.001.046.001 (Box Volume 46)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 74, 1968 -- 1969; UA037.001.047.001 (Box Volume 47)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 75, 1969 -- 1970; UA037.001.048.001 (Box Volume 48)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 76, 1970 -- 1971; UA037.001.049.001 (Box Volume 49)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 77, 1971 -- 1972; UA037.001.050.001 (Box Volume 50)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 78, 1972 -- 1973; UA037.001.051.001 (Box Volume 51)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 79, 1973 -- 1974; UA037.001.052.001 (Box Volume 52)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 80, 1974 -- 1975; UA037.001.053.001 (Box Volume 53)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 81, 1975 -- 1976; UA037.001.054.001 (Box Volume 54)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 82, 1976 -- 1977; UA037.001.055.001 (Box Volume 55)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 83, 1977 -- 1978; UA037.001.056.001 (Box Volume 56)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 84, 1978 -- 1979; UA037.001.057.001 (Box Volume 57)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 85, 1979 -- 1980; UA037.001.058.001 (Box Volume 58)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 86, 1980 -- 1981; UA037.001.059.001 (Box Volume 59)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 87, 1981 -- 1982; UA037.001.060.001 (Box Volume 60)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 88, 1982 -- 1983; UA037.001.061.001 (Box Volume 61)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 89, 1983 -- 1984; UA037.001.062.001 (Box Volume 62)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 90, 1984 -- 1985; UA037.001.063.001 (Box Volume 63)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 91, 1985 -- 1986; UA037.001.064.001 (Box Volume 64)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 92, 1986 -- 1987; UA037.001.065.001 (Box Volume 65)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 93, 1987 -- 1988; UA037.001.066.001 (Box Volume 66)
  - College of Engineering, 1987 -- 1988; UA037.001.067.00001 (Box 67)
  - Special Studies, 1987 -- 1988; UA037.001.067.00002 (Box 67)
  - BSOT faculty meetings, 1987 -- 1988; UA037.001.067.00003 (Box 67)
  - Liberal Arts/Jackson, 1987 -- 1988; UA037.001.067.00004 (Box 67)
  - Graduate School, 1987 -- 1988; UA037.001.067.00005 (Box 67)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1988-89 (1 of 2), 1988 -- 1989; UA037.001.067.00006 (Box 67)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1988-89 (2 of 2), 1988 -- 1989; UA037.001.067.00007 (Box 67)
  - College of Engineering, 1988 -- 1989; UA037.001.067.00008 (Box 67)
  - Special Studies, 1988 -- 1989; UA037.001.067.00009 (Box 67)
  - BSOT Faculty Meetings, 1988 -- 1989; UA037.001.067.00010 (Box 67)
  - Liberal Arts/Jackson, 1988 -- 1989; UA037.001.067.00011 (Box 67)
  - Graduate School, 1988 -- 1989; UA037.001.067.00012 (Box 67)
  - Faculty GSAS, 1989 -- 1990; UA037.001.067.00013 (Box 67)
  - Faculty Liberal Arts and Jackson, 1989 -- 1990; UA037.001.067.00014 (Box 67)
  - Faculty Arts and Sciences, 1989 -- 1990; UA037.001.067.00015 (Box 67)
  - College of Engineering, 1989 -- 1990; UA037.001.067.00016 (Box 67)
  - Special Studies, 1989 -- 1990; UA037.001.067.00017 (Box 67)
  - BSOT Faculty Meetings, 1989 -- 1990; UA037.001.067.00018 (Box 67)
  - Graduate School, 1989 -- 1990; UA037.001.067.00019 (Box 67)
  - Faculty records Arts and Sciences, faculty meetings, 1990-91 (1 of 2), 1990 -- 1991; UA037.001.067.00020 (Box 67)
  - Faculty records Arts and Sciences, faculty meetings, 1990-91 (2 of 2), 1990 -- 1991; UA037.001.067.00021 (Box 67)
  - Faculty records College of Special Studies faculty meetings, 1990 -- 1991; UA037.001.067.00022 (Box 67)
  - Faculty records Engineering faculty meetings, 1990 -- 1991; UA037.001.067.00023 (Box 67)
  - Faculty records Liberal Arts and Jackson faculty meetings, 1990 -- 1991; UA037.001.067.00024 (Box 67)
  - Faculty records Arts and Sciences Graduate School faculty meetings, 1990 -- 1991; UA037.001.067.00025 (Box 67)
  - College of Engineering, 1990 -- 1991; UA037.001.067.00026 (Box 67)
  - Special Studies, 1990 -- 1991; UA037.001.067.00027 (Box 67)
  - Graduate School, 1990 -- 1991; UA037.001.067.00028 (Box 67)
  - Engineering faculty meetings, 1991 -- 1992; UA037.001.067.00029 (Box 67)
  - Graduate School faculty meetings, 1991 -- 1992; UA037.001.067.00030 (Box 67)
  - Liberal Arts and Jackson faculty meetings, 1991 -- 1992; UA037.001.067.00031 (Box 67)
  - Special Studies faculty meetings, 1991 -- 1992; UA037.001.068.00001 (Box 68)
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meetings, 1991-92 (1 of 2), 1991 -- 1992; UA037.001.068.00002 (Box 68)
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meetings, 1991-92 (2 of 2), 1991 -- 1992; UA037.001.068.00003 (Box 68)
  - Special studies, 1991 -- 1992; UA037.001.068.00004 (Box 68)
  - Graduate school, 1991 -- 1992; UA037.001.068.00005 (Box 68)
  - Special Studies faculty meetings, 1992 -- 1993; UA037.001.068.00006 (Box 68)
  - Liberal Arts and Jackson faculty meetings, 1992 -- 1993; UA037.001.068.00007 (Box 68)
  - Graduate School of Arts and sciences faculty meetings, 1992 -- 1993; UA037.001.068.00008 (Box 68)
  - Engineering faculty meetings, 1992 -- 1993; UA037.001.068.00009 (Box 68)
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meetings, 1992 -- 1993; UA037.001.068.00010 (Box 68)
  - Special Studies, 1992 -- 1993; UA037.001.068.00011 (Box 68)
  - Graduate School, 1992 -- 1993; UA037.001.068.00012 (Box 68)
  - Special Studies faculty meetings, 1993 -- 1994; UA037.001.068.00013 (Box 68)
  - Liberal Arts and Jackson faculty meetings, 1993 -- 1994; UA037.001.068.00014 (Box 68)
  - Graduate School faculty meetings, 1993 -- 1994; UA037.001.068.00015 (Box 68)
  - Engineering faculty meetings, 1993 -- 1994; UA037.001.068.00016 (Box 68)
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meetings, 1993-94 (1 of 1), 1993 -- 1994; UA037.001.068.00017 (Box 68)
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meetings, 1993-94 (2 of 2), 1993 -- 1994; UA037.001.068.00018 (Box 68)
  - Special Studies, 1993 -- 1994; UA037.001.068.00019 (Box 68)
  - Graduate School, 1993 -- 1994; UA037.001.068.00020 (Box 68)
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meetings, 1994-95 (1 of 2), 1994 -- 1995; UA037.001.068.00021 (Box 68)
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meetings, 1994-95 (2 of 2), 1994 -- 1995; UA037.001.068.00022 (Box 68)
  - College of Engineering faculty meetings, 1994 -- 1995; UA037.001.068.00023 (Box 68)
  - College of Special Studies faculty meetings, 1994 -- 1995; UA037.001.068.00024 (Box 68)
  - Liberal Arts and Jackson faculty meetings,1994-95, 1994 -- 1995; UA037.001.068.00025 (Box 68)
  - Special Studies, 1994 -- 1995; UA037.001.068.00026 (Box 68)
  - Graduate Studies, 1994 -- 1995; UA037.001.068.00027 (Box 68)
  - Liberal Arts/Jackson, 1994 -- 1995; UA037.001.068.00028 (Box 68)
  - College of Engineering, 1994 -- 1995; UA037.001.068.00029 (Box 68)
  - Liberal Arts/Jackson,1995-96, 1995 -- 1996; UA037.001.068.00030 (Box 68)
  - Graduate Studies, 1995 -- 1996; UA037.001.068.00031 (Box 68)
  - Special Studies, 1995 -- 1996; UA037.001.068.00032 (Box 68)
  - College of Engineering, 1995 -- 1996; UA037.001.068.00033 (Box 68)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1995 -- 1996; UA037.001.069.00001 (Box 69)
  - Graduate Studies, 1996 -- 1997; UA037.001.069.00002 (Box 69)
  - College of Engineering, 1996 -- 1997; UA037.001.069.00003 (Box 69)
  - Special Studies, 1997; UA037.001.069.00004 (Box 69)
  - Liberal Arts and Jackson, 1996 -- 1997; UA037.001.069.00005 (Box 69)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1996 -- 1997; UA037.001.069.00006 (Box 69)
  - College of Engineering, 1997; UA037.001.069.00007 (Box 69)
  - Arts and Sciences, Liberal Arts and Jackson, Special Studies, 1997 -- 1998; UA037.001.069.00008 (Box 69)
  - Arts and Sciences, Liberal Arts and Jackson, Special Studies, 1997 -- 1998; UA037.001.069.00009 (Box 69)
  - Liberal Arts and Jackson faculty meetings, 1998 -- 1999; UA037.001.070.00001 (Box 70)
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meetings, 1998 -- 1999; UA037.001.070.00002 (Box 70)
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meetings, 1999; UA037.001.070.00003 (Box 70)
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meetings, 2000; UA037.001.070.00004 (Box 70)
  - Liberal Arts and Jackson faculty meetings, 1999 -- 2000; UA037.001.070.00005 (Box 70)
  - Special Studies faculty meetings, 1998 -- 1999; UA037.001.070.00006 (Box 70)
  - Special Studies faculty meetings, 1999 -- 2000; UA037.001.070.00007 (Box 70)
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering faculty meetings, 2000; UA037.001.071.00001 (Box 71)
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering faculty meetings, 2000 -- 2001; UA037.001.071.00002 (Box 71)
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering faculty meetings, 2001; UA037.001.071.00003 (Box 71)
  - Liberal Arts and Jackson faculty meetings, 2000 -- 2001; UA037.001.071.00004 (Box 71)
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, faculty meetings, 2001; UA037.001.071.00005 (Box 71)
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, faculty meetings, 2002; UA037.001.071.00006 (Box 71)
  - Faculty meetings, Liberal Arts and Jackson, 2001 -- 2002; UA037.001.072.00001 (Box 72)
  - Faculty meetings, School of Engineering, 2001 -- 2002; UA037.001.072.00002 (Box 72)
  - Faculty meetings, Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2001 -- 2002; UA037.001.072.00003 (Box 72)
  - Faculty meetings, Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2002; UA037.001.072.00004 (Box 72)
  - Faculty meetings, Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2002 -- 2003; UA037.001.072.00005 (Box 72)
  - Faculty meetings, Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2003; UA037.001.072.00006 (Box 72)
  - Faculty meetings, Liberal Arts and Jackson (A&S), 2002 -- 2003; UA037.001.072.00007 (Box 72)
  - Faculty meetings, School of Engineering, 2003; UA037.001.072.00008 (Box 72)
  - AS&E Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2003 -- 2004; UA037.001.072.00009 (Box 72)
  - AS&E Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2004; UA037.001.072.00010 (Box 72)
  - A&S (LA & J) Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2003 -- 2004; UA037.001.072.00011 (Box 72)
  - A&S (LA & J) Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2004; UA037.001.072.00012 (Box 72)
  - CSS Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2003; UA037.001.072.00013 (Box 72)
  - School of Engineering Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2003 -- 2004; UA037.001.072.00014 (Box 72)
  - GSAS Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2004; UA037.001.072.00015 (Box 72)
  - AS&E Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2004 -- 2005; UA037.001.072.00016 (Box 72)
  - AS&E Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2005; UA037.001.072.00017 (Box 72)
  - A&S Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2004 -- 2005; UA037.001.072.00018 (Box 72)
  - A&S Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2005; UA037.001.072.00019 (Box 72)
  - Engineering Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2005; UA037.001.072.00020 (Box 72)
  - GSAS Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2005; UA037.001.072.00021 (Box 72)
  - AS&E Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2005; UA037.001.072.00022 (Box 72)
  - AS&E Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2006; UA037.001.072.00023 (Box 72)
  - A&S Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2005 -- 2006; UA037.001.072.00024 (Box 72)
  - A&S Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2006; UA037.001.072.00025 (Box 72)
  - ENGG Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2005 -- 2006; UA037.001.072.00026 (Box 72)
  - GSAS Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2005 -- 2006; UA037.001.072.00027 (Box 72)
  - Tufts College Faculty Records, Vol. 73, 1967 -- 1968; UA037.001.073.00001 (Box Volume 73)
  - Reel No. 63-18: Tufts College Faculty Minutes, 1854 -- 1885; UA037.001.074.00001 (Box 74)
    Tufts College Faculty Minutes, Oct. 19, 1854-June 19, 1885; See also UA 193 -- University Microfilm -- Collection Documentation file in Digital Collections and Archives office
  - Reel No. 63-19: Tufts College Faculty Minutes, 1885 -- 1900; UA037.001.074.00002 (Box 74)
    Tufts College Faculty Minutes, Sept. 16, 1885-April 10, 1900; See also UA 193 -- University Microfilm -- Collection Documentation file in Digital Collections and Archives office
  - Reel No. 63-20: Tufts College Faculty Minutes, 1903 -- 1911; UA037.001.074.00003 (Box 74)
    Tufts College Facutly Minutes, March 3, 1903-1911; See also UA 193 -- University Microfilm -- Collection Documentation file in Digital Collections and Archives office
  - Reel No. 63-21: Tufts College Faculty Minutes, 1911 -- 1923; UA037.001.074.00004 (Box 74)
    Tufts College Faculty Minutes 1911-23; See also UA 193 -- University Microfilm -- Collection Documentation file in Digital Collections and Archives office
  - Reel No. 63-22: Tufts College Faculty Minutes, 1923 -- 1935; UA037.001.074.00005 (Box 74)
    Faculties and Committees 1923/24; See also UA 193 -- University Microfilm -- Collection Documentation file in Digital Collections and Archives office
  - Reel No. 63-23: Tufts College Faculty Minutes, 1935 -- 1945; UA037.001.074.00006 (Box 74)
    See also UA 193 -- University Microfilm -- Collection Documentation file in Digital Collections and Archives office
  - Reel No. 63-24: Tufts College Faculty Minutes, 1945 -- 1955; UA037.001.074.00007 (Box 74)
  - Reel No. 63-25: Tufts College Faculty Minutes, 1955 -- 1961; UA037.001.074.00008 (Box 74)
  - Reel No. 63-26: Tufts College Faculty Official Papers, 1892 -- 1925; UA037.001.074.00009 (Box 74)
  - Reel No. 83: Faculty Minutes, 1967 -- 1970; UA037.001.074.00010 (Box 74)
    Faculty Minutes START: Vol. 73 1967-1968, Vol. 74 1968-1969 END: Vol. 75 1969-1970 Book 1 and 2; See also UA 193 -- University Microfilm -- Collection Documentation file in Digital Collections and Archives office
  - Reel No. 84: Faculty Minutes, 1970 -- 1974; UA037.001.074.00011 (Box 74)
    Faculty Minutes START: Vol 76 1970-1971, Vol. 77 1971-1972, Vol. 78 1972-1973, END: Vol. 79 1973-1974; See also UA 193 -- University Microfilm -- Collection Documentation file in Digital Collections and Archives office
  - Reel No. 105: Faculty Minutes, 1974 -- 1978; UA037.001.074.00012 (Box 74)
    Faculty Minutes START: 1974-1975, 1975-1976, 1976-1977 END: July 1977-May 1978; See also UA 193 -- University Microfilm -- Collection Documentation file in Digital Collections and Archives office
  - Reel No. 126: Faculty Minutes, 1980 -- 1982; UA037.001.074.00013 (Box 74)
    Tufts University Faculty Minutes START: Volume 86 Ser. 3.1 1980-1981 END Volume 87 Ser. 3.1 1981-1982; See also UA 193 -- University Microfilm -- Collection Documentation file in Digital Collections and Archives office
  - Reel No. 136: Faculty Minutes, 1982 -- 1984; UA037.001.074.00014 (Box 74)
    Tufts University Faculty Minutes START: Vol. 88 82/83 END: Fac. Vol. 89 83/84; See also UA 193 -- University Microfilm -- Collection Documentation file in Digital Collections and Archives office
  - A, S and E, 2006 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00001 (Box 76)
    75 years from the date of creation.
  - A, S and E, 2006 -- 2009; UA037.001.076.00002 (Box 76)
  - A, S and E, 2006 -- 2011; UA037.001.076.00003 (Box 76)
  - A, S and E, 2006 -- 2011; UA037.001.076.00004 (Box 76)
  - A, S and E, 2006 -- 2012; UA037.001.076.00005 (Box 76)
  - A, S and E, 2001 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00006 (Box 76)
  - A, S and E, 2002 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00007 (Box 76)
  - A, S and E, 2003 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00008 (Box 76)
  - A, S and E, 2004 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00009 (Box 76)
  - A, S and E, 2005 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00010 (Box 76)
  - A and S, 2006 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00011 (Box 76)
    No minutes in this section.
  - A and S, 2006 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00012 (Box 76)
  - A and S, 2006 -- 2011; UA037.001.076.00013 (Box 76)
  - A and S, 2006 -- 2012; UA037.001.076.00014 (Box 76)
  - A and S, 2001 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00015 (Box 76)
  - A and S, 2001 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00016 (Box 76)
  - A and S, 2002 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00017 (Box 76)
  - A and S, 2004 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00018 (Box 76)
  - A and S, 2004 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00019 (Box 76)
  - A and S, 2005 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00020 (Box 76)
  - A and S, 2005 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00021 (Box 76)
  - ENGG, 2006 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00022 (Box 76)
  - ENGG, 2006 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00023 (Box 76)
  - ENGG, 2006 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00024 (Box 76)
  - ENGG, 2006 -- 2012; UA037.001.076.00025 (Box 76)
  - ENGG, 2001 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00026 (Box 76)
  - ENGG, 2001 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00027 (Box 76)
  - ENGG, 2002 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00028 (Box 76)
  - ENGG, 2004 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00029 (Box 76)
  - ENGG, 2004 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00030 (Box 76)
  - ENGG, 2005 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00031 (Box 76)
  - ENGG, 2005 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00032 (Box 76)
  - ENGG, 2005 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00033 (Box 76)
  - GSAS, 2006 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00034 (Box 76)
  - GSAS, 2006 -- 2011; UA037.001.076.00035 (Box 76)
  - GSAS, 2001 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00036 (Box 76)
  - GSAS, 2005 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00037 (Box 76)
  - CSS, 2006 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00038 (Box 76)
  - CSS, 2006 -- 2011; UA037.001.076.00039 (Box 76)
  - CSS, 2001 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00040 (Box 76)